{
  "Questions":[
    {
      "Qno":1, 
      "question":"Which of the following is a superclass of every class in Java?",
      "option1":"ArrayList",
      "option2":"Object class",
      "option3":"Abstract class",
      "option4":"String"
    },
    {
      "Qno":2, 
      "question":"What is the size of float variable?",
      "option1":"8 bit",
      "option2":"16 bit",
      "option3":"32 bit",
      "option4":"64 bit"
    },
    {
      "Qno":3, 
      "question":"Which will legally declare, construct, and initialize an array?",
      "option1":"int [] myList = {'1', '2', '3'};",
      "option2":"int [] myList = (5, 8, 2);",
      "option3":"int myList [] [] = {4,9,7,0};",
      "option4":"int myList [] = {4, 3, 7};"
    },
    {
      "Qno":4, 
      "question":"Suppose that you would like to create an instance of a new Map that has an iteration order that is the same as the iteration order of an existing instance of a Map. Which concrete implementation of the Map interface should be used for the new instance?",
      "option1":"TreeMap",
      "option2":"HashMap",
      "option3":"LinkedHashMap",
      "option4":"The answer depends on the implementation of the existing instance."
    },
    {
      "Qno":5, 
      "question":"What is the size of double in java",
      "option1":"32",
      "option2":"64",
      "option3":"8",
      "option4":"16"
    },
    {
      "Qno":6, 
      "question":"If result = 2 + 3 * 5, what is the value and type of ‘result’ variable?",
      "option1":"17, byte",
      "option2":"25, byte",
      "option3":"17, int",
      "option4":"25, int"
    },
    {
      "Qno":7, 
      "question":"How many numeric data types are supported in Java?",
      "option1":"8",
      "option2":"4",
      "option3":"2",
      "option4":"6"
    },
    {
      "Qno":8, 
      "question":"The class java.lang.Exception is",
      "option1":"Protected",
      "option2":"Extends Throwable",
      "option3":"Implements Throwable",
      "option4":"Serializable"
    },
    {
      "Qno":9, 
      "question":"Arrays in java are",
      "option1":"Object references",
      "option2":"Objects",
      "option3":"Primitive types",
      "option4":"None"
    },
    {
      "Qno":10, 
      "question":"Which of the following is synchronized?",
      "option1":"Set",
      "option2":"LinkedList",
      "option3":"Vector",
      "option4":"WeakHashMap"
    }
  ],
  "Answers":[
    {"qno":1, "ans":2},
    {"qno":2, "ans":3},
    {"qno":3, "ans":4},
    {"qno":4, "ans":3},
    {"qno":5, "ans":2},
    {"qno":6, "ans":3},
    {"qno":7, "ans":4},
    {"qno":8, "ans":2},
    {"qno":9, "ans":2},
    {"qno":10, "ans":3}
]
  }